Here is how to provision and activate an ARCANE user.
ARCANE—Adaptive Runtime for
Cognitive AI Native Environments—
currently runs on both Microsoft NT
and the Linux kernel,
supporting regulated environments
as well as personal devices.
Android support is under development.
This demonstration shows the
Microsoft NT Provisioner.
On Linux, follow host-specific instructions;
identity and privilege steps can differ.
Sign in as an authorized administrator.
Open the trusted Provisioner, refresh status,
and review its readiness checks.
Complete the verified machine baseline first.
Under Create ARCANE users,
enter the intended account name.
Do not choose the administrator account
running the Provisioner.
Select Create ARCANE user.
A new Microsoft NT account is staged
as a disabled standard user,
assigned ARCANE Shell,
and given a temporary password.
An existing standard account keeps
its password and memberships.
Save any new credential privately
for the intended user.
Never place it in chat, email, documentation,
logs, or source control,
and never show it in a recording.
Once the credential is secure,
select Activate this account.
Activation is a separate privileged step;
creation does not silently enable the account.
Sign out of the administrator session.
Let the user sign in, change the temporary
password when prompted,
and verify ARCANE Shell opens.
Check Settings, logout,
and the documented recovery path.
If activation is interrupted, leave the account
staged and retry in the Provisioner.
Follow the target host's release guidance.
Provisioning and activation are complete.
The new user can begin in ARCANE, with a clear
handoff and a recoverable path forward.