Welcome to ARCANE OS.
ARCANE stands for Adaptive Runtime for Cognitive AI Native Environments.
It is an AI-native operating environment designed around what a person is trying to accomplish,
not around finding the right app, file, or sequence of menus.
Under ARCANE, intent, context, memory, policy, and capabilities work together.
You express a goal.
ARCANE helps assemble the approved tools and information needed to move that goal forward,
while keeping important actions visible and governed by the permissions of the person and the device.
ARCANE is not a chatbot pasted onto a desktop.
It is the environment through which people and intelligent systems work with the computer.
The familiar shell, settings, documents, and specialized applications remain available,
but they are connected through a shared runtime and capability boundary.
Today, ARCANE runs above both Microsoft NT and the Linux kernel.
That makes it adaptable to the controls of a regulated workplace and to the needs of a personal device.
The underlying platform supplies drivers, identity, processes, and hardware access.
ARCANE supplies the consistent experience and governed collaboration layer.
Android support is currently under development.
The result is one environment that can serve engineers, operators, families, security teams,
and mission-focused organizations without asking every user to become a systems expert.
ARCANE asks a different question.
How should humans and intelligent systems work together?
Explore the shell, open an application, and begin with the outcome you want to achieve.
Welcome to ARCANE.