Welcome to ARCANE OS.
ARCANE stands for Adaptive Runtime for
Cognitive AI Native Environments.
It is an AI-native operating environment designed
around what a person is trying to accomplish,
not around finding the right app, file,
or sequence of menus.
Under ARCANE, intent, context, memory, policy,
and capabilities work together.
You express a goal.
ARCANE helps assemble the approved tools and
information needed to move that goal forward,
while keeping important actions visible and governed
by the permissions of the person and the device.
ARCANE is not a chatbot pasted onto a desktop.
It is the environment through which people and
intelligent systems work with the computer.
The familiar shell, settings, documents, and
specialized applications remain available,
but they are connected through a shared runtime
and capability boundary.
ARCANE currently runs on both Microsoft NT
and the Linux kernel.
That makes it adaptable to the controls of a regulated
workplace and to the needs of a personal device.
The underlying platform supplies drivers, identity,
processes, and hardware access.
ARCANE supplies the consistent experience
and governed collaboration layer.
Android support is currently under development.
The result is one environment that can serve engineers,
operators, families, security teams,
and mission-focused organizations without asking
every user to become a systems expert.
ARCANE asks a different question.
How should humans and intelligent systems
work together?
Explore the shell, open an application, and begin
with the outcome you want to achieve.
Welcome to ARCANE.